<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Aclevo</title><description>The official blog of Aclevo.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Aclevo</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 2.13</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 02:31:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>LateralGM: An Open Source to GameMaker</title><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let's face it, Game Maker (the one by YoYo Games) can cost a bit of money if you want to remove their branding when you publish a game. While some people are okay with having their branding on the game, others may wish to remove it without having to&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/lateralgm-an-open-source-alternative-to-gamemaker/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c622800b509254e737cef37</guid><category>gaming</category><category>game</category><category>open source</category><category>development</category><category>review</category><category>LateralGM</category><category>Game Maker</category><category>YoYo Games</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 02:31:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let's face it, Game Maker (the one by YoYo Games) can cost a bit of money if you want to remove their branding when you publish a game. While some people are okay with having their branding on the game, others may wish to remove it without having to spend a fortune doing so. However, why pay for the software when there's an open source alternative already available that looks almost exactly like the original software. But why would you consider an open source alternative adequate?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-lateralgm-is-it-stable"&gt;Why LateralGM? Is it Stable?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;With LateralGM, you get all of the features that Game Maker for free. On top of that, all of the code is public on GitHub. You can find all the code available &lt;a href="http://localhost:2368/lateralgm-an-open-source-alternative-to-gamemaker/github.com/enigma-dev/enigma-dev"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Cloning the repository there to install the software is recommended, and is the best way we found to use the software. While it basically works just like Game Maker (8) would, there are some takeaways from using this over YoYo Game's version. Here is just some of the differences we found:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There are still some bugs that still need to be worked out. For instance, the built-in editor for working with in-game sprites doesn't function well. A workaround is to use an external program to work with the game's objects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your code will be compiled using C++ and Make. You can even read the output to make sure your game is not executing any bad code. This however will cost you some time to compile.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The user interface will look a little different to what you are expecting, as the front-end uses JDK (Java Development Kit) to display the User Interface. While you can customize it a little, they are apparently working on a new solution that uses QT, the same framework that powers KDE (a desktop for Linux).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 id="conclusion"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether to decide between open source software and paying for a commercial product is always a debate. We believe however, that consumers should this alternative first before going to pick up YoYo Game's version of Game Maker. You might just save a few hundred dollars if you decide this version is adequate for your requirements. Plus, you get to see all the code you are compiling before you release your project to the open world, which may get more users' trust.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Landy's Farm - The Trailer</title><description>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;iframe width="480" height="270" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ox0yJ8N3eCw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I first started listening to the song that would later be used in this video, I already had an idea on what kind of video I was going to make. Even the title of the song is called "At The Farm", which gave me this idea of recording a&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/landys-farm-the-trailer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5e2872d5aa343dc7235a7d</guid><category>trailer</category><category>gaming</category><category>farm</category><category>landy</category><category>minecraft</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 01:17:02 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1495107334309-fcf20504a5ab?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;iframe width="480" height="270" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ox0yJ8N3eCw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1495107334309-fcf20504a5ab?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" alt="Landy's Farm - The Trailer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I first started listening to the song that would later be used in this video, I already had an idea on what kind of video I was going to make. Even the title of the song is called "At The Farm", which gave me this idea of recording a trailer of a farm. A bit of time later when I played Minecraft, I met someone on the Railway Craft Server known as Landy, who would often give me in-game food to help me with my travels. Curious to see what was behind the action, I asked him about how he would get all of this food, and he said he grew it as this very barn. After getting a consent to record this awesomeness, I took out my in-game camera and recorded what would be known as the Landy's Farm Trailer. Please enjoy this short!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Baylandia Trailer (Minecraft Town by Scythal)</title><description>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;iframe width="480" height="270" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O-uNC0RsBEM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;One day I was talking to a friend, who later would become an Aclevo Member, who suggested I come on a Minecraft Server and check out his town. I decided it would make a nice video to record, so I loaded up OBS and hopped on to check it out.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/bylandia-town-minecraft-town-by-scythal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5c6c83ff84180dd6eeab8f</guid><category>minecraft</category><category>town</category><category>Bylandia</category><category>video game</category><category>video</category><category>review</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 17:45:31 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1544289142-24eacdfed7de?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;iframe width="480" height="270" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O-uNC0RsBEM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1544289142-24eacdfed7de?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" alt="Baylandia Trailer (Minecraft Town by Scythal)"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One day I was talking to a friend, who later would become an Aclevo Member, who suggested I come on a Minecraft Server and check out his town. I decided it would make a nice video to record, so I loaded up OBS and hopped on to check it out. I was amazed by this work, and recorded what would become  the "Bayland Trailer". As one of the only videos I worked on using LightWorks Video Editor, the results were very nice. Check out the results in the video above and let us know what you think.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Aclevo's 2019</title><description>&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h1 id="happy-new-year-everyone-"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Happy New Year everyone!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of this blog post, today is January 1st, 2019. Aclevo is going to be taking a huge turn to good this year. I, as your new Co-Owner &amp;amp; Secretary, will strive to make Aclevo take a huge turn this year. My goal for Aclevo is&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/aclevos-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a22f4166677428a84f23d</guid><category>Aclevo</category><category>2019</category><category>new years</category><category>resolutions</category><category>change</category><category>legacy</category><category>achievements</category><category>blog</category><category>annoucements</category><dc:creator>TheCodingGuy</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1521478413868-1bbd982fa4a5?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h1 id="happy-new-year-everyone-"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Happy New Year everyone!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1521478413868-1bbd982fa4a5?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" alt="Aclevo's 2019"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of this blog post, today is January 1st, 2019. Aclevo is going to be taking a huge turn to good this year. I, as your new Co-Owner &amp;amp; Secretary, will strive to make Aclevo take a huge turn this year. My goal for Aclevo is to make Aclevo run, even after Reasonably Selenium decides to step down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aclevo's 2019 will be the best year for Aclevo. This year, we will be assigning more fun and just-right tasks for our members. We accept anyone who is willing to join our awesome group (&lt;strong&gt;Reminder:&lt;/strong&gt; We aren't a company and we don't plan to become one anytime soon).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other news, let me not get blown away by leftover fireworks people are shooting for World War 3 here, and continue on Aclevo's legacy!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your new Co-Owner and Secretary, TheCodingGuy.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Super Smash Bros Ultimate [Review]</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Well, before too many people make me look like a bumhole, I want to say that Smash Bros is a really fun and generally accepted Video Game series, and the latest addition to the series is one of the best of the best at this time! With a campaign mode&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/super-smash-bros-ultimate-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a32791fa13f590f5284c4</guid><category>super smash bros</category><category>video game</category><category>nintendo switch</category><category>nintendo</category><category>online membership</category><category>artifical intelligence</category><dc:creator>Anonymous</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 01:05:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1548003693-b55d51032288?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1548003693-b55d51032288?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" alt="Super Smash Bros Ultimate [Review]"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, before too many people make me look like a bumhole, I want to say that Smash Bros is a really fun and generally accepted Video Game series, and the latest addition to the series is one of the best of the best at this time! With a campaign mode where you go around the world, collecting spirits and saving the fighters of Smash Bros. To a fun multi-player mode where you can face off against the computer or play with your friends in local play, to also an online mode which I haven't even checked out yet due to not having a Switch Online membership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But all and all the game is one of the best titles that I have played in a long time, it's just the game my mind has been craving and wanting for several long years yet to come. The light sensation that I get with this game makes me feel a lot better compared to the heavy sensation I get with most every other game which means that the game doesn't trigger my stress as much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The character roster for Smash Bros of course brings back every character from Smash History, along with some new faces as well, such as King K Rool as an example. I'm still working on unlocking all the characters myself and I love it when I funally get one unlocked, the satisfying feeling is just so good!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyway I would rate Smash Ultimate a very solid 10 out of 10, Just because I've never had so much fun in a very long time.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Welcome Back to Aclevo</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, and welcome back to Aclevo. I'm the founder and owner, Reasonably Selenium, and we have some great updates for you all. Be sure to stay tuned to learn out what's been going on, what's in store, and what you missed. There's a lot that's happened between the 6&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/welcome-back-to-aclevo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a350a1fa13f590f528508</guid><category>annoucements</category><category>achievements</category><category>goals</category><category>Aclevo</category><category>Dorper</category><category>history</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 18:15:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1533745848184-3db07256e163?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1533745848184-3db07256e163?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" alt="Welcome Back to Aclevo"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, and welcome back to Aclevo. I'm the founder and owner, Reasonably Selenium, and we have some great updates for you all. Be sure to stay tuned to learn out what's been going on, what's in store, and what you missed. There's a lot that's happened between the 6 months since the time we were acquired by Dorper, and we feel it's important for everyone to know what happened to us at that time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="our-achievements-of-the-past"&gt;Our Achievements Of The Past&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ever since 2015, Aclevo has been uniting people around the world to work together and make cool things. With over fifty overall members that have come and gone, Aclevo has been known for it's long history of encouraging people to express themselves and their inner talent to make the world a better place. We have encouraged those who were and are in difficult times to find an outlet of content creation to, in return, create hope for those who need it and distract those from their pain they experience in real life. We, therefore, have helped those with depression from turning to something that hurt or kill them in the end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, that's not the only thing that Aclevo has done to help and support people as a whole. We've also work with people to work toward their personal goals, whether it's learning to produce great videos, snapping good photos, making great music, and teaching media skills in today's modern world of technology. In reponse, they have the means to go out into the real world and establish a great career in what they love to do. Reaching those goals benefits not only our community, but the entire Earth in general, reducing poverty and giving people a means to work together for the better of all of us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="dorper-acquisation-comeback"&gt;Dorper Acquisation &amp;amp; Comeback&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around six to seven months ago, our website started to redirect to the Dorper Website. This is because we were acquired by Dorper during that time. According to a blog post on Dorper's Website, Aclevo had been acquired by Dorper at that time. However, with a special agreement between both of me and Dorper's owner, Carver, we were able to restore full condition and services provided we added a backlink somewhere on the website. We absolutely thank them for allowing us to restore full ownership and become a family again. But why would Aclevo be given away to Dorper in the first place? There were a few reasons that this action was required at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the reasons for the necesity of Aclevo's acquisation into Dorper is because I was unable to preside during the time. Due to a few personal issues going on in my life, I was simply unable to stabily control the group at that time. I was simply too occupied to be able to successfully control it, and therefore had to give it to someone. Besides this, Aclevo had unsuccessfully been in another merger which caused instability in the group. While we wish to explain what happened, the appropriate group manager for that organization would like to maintain anonymity about the situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="what-s-next"&gt;What's Next?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this time, we are currently focusing on rebuilding the website to a stable condition. We are also working on specifics that are unable to be released at this time. We wish to continue any projects and series that are appropriate for the restart of our family, however it is not currently the top priority as the website at this time. This is to ensure our website will be available in a presentable manner. We promise to start releasing new content once we are ready to do so, but we ask that our viewers be patient so we can ensure that we are able to stand on our two feet, so to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone is free to offer assistance to our group if they wish to do so. &lt;a href="https://aclevo.xyz/contact"&gt;Here is a link to the contact form to submit a request.&lt;/a&gt; We appreciate those with web programming experience to volunteer for us so we can focus on our other content. Please allow up to 3 business days for a reply from our staff to consider your request. We appreciate your patience and are delighted to gain more support to keep us afloat. Another way to support us is to give feedback, donating (not available yet, perhaps soon), and spreading the word about us to increase our viewership. Even just sharing this article is a great way to help us out in the long run, to make sure people find this article and check us out. While is it not required, we thank you for deciding to assist us in any way you all can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="conclusion"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are very excited to be back together as a family and to unite people around the world together to make a difference. We hope to inspire people like never before to create content and to help spread happiness and unity among all peoples, no matter who you are as a person. Supporting others and making a difference brings happiness to those who really need it. Aclevo's main goal is to bring people together to create a great community, and to give them hope to create content and show the world their inner talents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading this article and giving us your support. Please feel free to share this article with your friends, and spread the news that Aclevo is back for good this time.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Becoming An Adult: An Introduction</title><description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Reasonably Selenium, and I am almost an adult, but I am still living at my parent's house. I have no source of income right now, and I need to save up so I don't end up in a cardboard box in the next decade. YouTube is not&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/becoming-an-adult-an-introduction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a33211fa13f590f5284d3</guid><category>job</category><category>adult</category><category>introduction</category><category>money</category><category>transitioning</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/job-seekers_11487588.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/job-seekers_11487588.jpg" alt="Becoming An Adult: An Introduction"&gt;&lt;p&gt;My name is Reasonably Selenium, and I am almost an adult, but I am still living at my parent's house. I have no source of income right now, and I need to save up so I don't end up in a cardboard box in the next decade. YouTube is not going to be a solution anymore, especially because of the new requirements they are enforcing. The blog itself isn't going to make me enough money to live on my own either. I have to grow up, get a job, and learn the essentials of becoming an adult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I will be keeping track of my progress of becoming an adult on this new blog series. This way, people who want to follow my story can check out new releases, and possibly learn about what it feels like to transition to the real world. I have a lot to learn about, and my knowledge has only touched the surface of the many necessities I will need to look out for. My past work experiences and current course in finances should help me reach my personal educational goals, and I hope to expand my learning by going to college. But getting a job and not catching &lt;em&gt;writer's block&lt;/em&gt; has to come first before I get there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to volunteer at a few restaurants in order to feel how working at a job really is. From October 2014 to May 2015, I have worked at Subway, Chili's, CVS Pharmacy, and even the library. They had me do several chores there; such as washing dishes, packaging food, sweeping the floor, cleaning the windows, putting products on the shelf, and taking out the trash. These experiences will help me get a real job and earn some money so I can advance my education. I will then be able to pursue the career I wish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selecting a college will be a great challenge I will face. Hopefully, a smaller college will be an option for me when I get my scholarships. If not, I will have to go to a community college while I work trying to save up money for one. My parents have left me a savings account which contains money I will need in case something fails. But I would rather select the right one and pursue getting good grades. Once I complete college, I will be able to get into my career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This marks the end of this post. I do not have much to say as I have not really made any progress yet. Aclevo is one of my biggest priorities, but I need money in order to keep the lights on when I get older. I also have to finish school before I start going to a college or get a job, as my grades are very important to me. I also have to see a couple of doctors to make sure I'm physically ready to become an adult, and if not get my health fixed so I can be ready. Thanks for reading this post!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How To Remove Your Facebook &amp; Why You Should</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re reading this article you may have considered deleting your Facebook account before, but you're worried. Worried about missing out, struggling to stay connected, or getting left behind by the almost 2 billion users on Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg's platform. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don't be. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has never before been easier&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/how-to-remove-your-facebook-why-you-should/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a2cf81fa13f590f528446</guid><category>facebook</category><category>privacy</category><category>security</category><category>internet</category><category>delete</category><category>social media</category><dc:creator>RXDesigns</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/fbheaderimg-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/fbheaderimg-1.jpg" alt="How To Remove Your Facebook &amp; Why You Should"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re reading this article you may have considered deleting your Facebook account before, but you're worried. Worried about missing out, struggling to stay connected, or getting left behind by the almost 2 billion users on Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg's platform. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don't be. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has never before been easier to completely remove Facebook from your life — not missing a single social beat in the process. And when you finally do, you'll wonder what took you so long in the first place. In case you’re wondering why you should delete your Facebook, &lt;a href="https://np.reddit.com/r/AntiFacebook/wiki/index"&gt;here’s a list of all the bad things Facebook has done since 2007&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="first-things-first-hitting-delete"&gt;First things first: Hitting "delete"&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're going to live without Facebook your first step should be actually deleting your account. Thankfully, it's not that tricky. Kick off the liberating process by logging into your Facebook account. Savor the knowledge that this will be the last time you ever need to do this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, instead of navigating your way through a bunch of random menus, simply drop &lt;a href="http://2.aclevo.xyz/how-to-remove-facebook/www.facebook.com/help/delete_account/index.html"&gt;www.facebook.com/help/delete_account&lt;/a&gt; into your address bar (or just click the hyperlink). Select "Delete My Account," follow the steps, and you're good to go. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wasn't that easy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="your-social-life-after-facebook"&gt;Your social life after Facebook&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;So you're free. What next? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is where it gets interesting. Zuckerberg likes to talk about making the world "a more open and connected place," and if Facebook does indeed do that, then deleting your Facebook account might theoretically make your personal world less open and less connected. But it doesn't have to be that way. Instead, a Facebook-free life has the potential to be just the opposite. Sure, you may not be "friends" with two thousand people any more, but were you ever really in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dropping Facebook gives you the time and space to actually go plumb those relationship depths. No more checking up on an old friend by doing a quick profile flyby. Instead, if you want to know how the birth of their first-born child went, you'll ask them directly. And they'll respond. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still not convinced you won't be missing out? Here's how the first few days of your Facebook-free life will go down: A friend or family member will try to scope on your vacation pics or invite you to an event on Facebook. They will, of course, not be able to find your account. What happens next is magical. That same friend or family member will hit you up directly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, Facebook is a chore, and one that you don't have to do. Because I'm telling you from experience, living a post-Facebook life is easy if you make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Vegan Dairy-Free Oreo Milkshake (Ice Cream Optional)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you crave milkshakes, but can't digest milk? As a person who cannot digest milk, I had the same problem as you, so I needed to find a good alternative that would satisfy my stomach. Looking around, I found the best way to make a milkshake without the milk, while&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/vegan-dairy-free-oreo-milkshake-ice-cream-optional/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a33871fa13f590f5284df</guid><category>vegan</category><category>diary free</category><category>milkshake</category><category>oreo</category><category>ice cream</category><category>bananas</category><category>chocolate</category><category>milk allergy</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1523754116966-300250e98597?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1523754116966-300250e98597?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" alt="Vegan Dairy-Free Oreo Milkshake (Ice Cream Optional)"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you crave milkshakes, but can't digest milk? As a person who cannot digest milk, I had the same problem as you, so I needed to find a good alternative that would satisfy my stomach. Looking around, I found the best way to make a milkshake without the milk, while still finding a way to adding fruit into the mix. Here is a list of ingredients that you will need to get started.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chocolate Soy Milk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Frozen Bananas&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oreo Cookies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chocolate Syrup (OPTIONAL, enhances taste)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chocolate Soy Ice Cream (OPTIONAL, enhances thickness)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOTICE: Please feel free to experiment the measurements to your liking. When I made this recipe up, I experimented with quantities to see what tastes best for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A blender is highly recommended for the best blend of your milkshake. Blending this by hand may be very tough, depending on how strong you are. Please let me know down in the comments section how it turns out if you perform these steps without a blender. Also feel free to send links of your shakes in the comments section below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that you have all the ingredients, here is how you make your tasty milkshake: &lt;br&gt;1. Place all of the ingredients above into a blender. If the ingredient is in a container, use common sense. Blending the containers in with your drink may result in injury, or at least a bad time. &lt;br&gt;2. Blend until a thick texture can be seen. No large crumbs should be in the shake. &lt;br&gt;3. If you need an example for step 2, look at the cover image above. &lt;br&gt;4. If you want to add in the chocolate syrup after you blend, it's okay. Just pour it in. &lt;br&gt;5. Your milkshake is now ready for consumption. Enjoy. ;)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Discord's New Policies - How They Affect You</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Just recently, Discord released new policies regarding text channels and personal messages. These changes include a new &lt;strong&gt;Report&lt;/strong&gt; button, a new &lt;strong&gt;Community Guidelines&lt;/strong&gt; policy, and restricting access to minors from using the service. The Privacy Policy and Terms Of Service were modified to reflect those changes. Here are five changes&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/discords-new-policies-how-they-affect-you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a34351fa13f590f5284f2</guid><category>discord</category><category>policy</category><category>text messaging</category><category>privacy</category><category>community guidelines</category><category>reporting</category><category>age requirements</category><category>advertising</category><category>data collection</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 17:50:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/1-oEsKvHEupyHLT1EmhUeVAA.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/1-oEsKvHEupyHLT1EmhUeVAA.png" alt="Discord's New Policies - How They Affect You"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just recently, Discord released new policies regarding text channels and personal messages. These changes include a new &lt;strong&gt;Report&lt;/strong&gt; button, a new &lt;strong&gt;Community Guidelines&lt;/strong&gt; policy, and restricting access to minors from using the service. The Privacy Policy and Terms Of Service were modified to reflect those changes. Here are five changes to expect with Discord.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="1-reporting-users-is-now-easier"&gt;1. Reporting Users Is Now Easier&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card"&gt;&lt;img src="https://support.discordapp.com/hc/article_attachments/115000262372/ReportMenuStuff.png" class="kg-image" alt="Discord's New Policies - How They Affect You"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Discord's New Report Screen, as posted &lt;a href="https://support.discordapp.com/hc/en-us/articles/115000083792"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;From here, you can select from several different reasons to be sent to the Discord abuse team for review. The following reasons are provided: Illegal Content, Harassment, Spam or Phishing Links, Self Harm, or NSFW (&lt;em&gt;Not Safe For Work&lt;/em&gt;) content. More information on the following reasons can be found on &lt;a href="https://support.discordapp.com/hc/en-us/articles/115000083792"&gt;this article about how to report a user&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://blog.discordapp.com/safety-boost-part-two-7b9069428437"&gt;this article about the recent changes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="2-nsfw-content-is-now-hidden"&gt;2. NSFW Content Is Now Hidden&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*EHs5sUhiuBPQJLVubZ5foA.png" class="kg-image" alt="Discord's New Policies - How They Affect You"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The new NSFW Channel Notice, found &lt;a href="https://blog.discordapp.com/safety-boost-part-two-7b9069428437"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;From here, users may continue to see this content. Users may also click "&lt;strong&gt;Nope&lt;/strong&gt;" as described above if they do not wish to see the content. They will be sent to the general chat room, whether or not modifications to that channel were made or not. This means that users may be sent back to the announcements or rules instead of the main chat if general was used for that purpose. Also note that according to the image above, users that are under the age of eighteen (18) will not be allowed to look at this content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="3-discord-new-age-requirement"&gt;3. Discord New Age Requirement&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additions to the Privacy Policy require users to be thirteen (13) or older in order to be able to sign up for a Discord Account. In order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, otherwise known as "&lt;strong&gt;COPPA&lt;/strong&gt;", Discord is not allowed to knowingly collect personal information on children under the age of thirteen (13). Parents who believe that their children may have exposed personal information may contact Discord staff &lt;a href="http://2.aclevo.xyz/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection.html#384b4d4848574a4c785c514b5b574a5c594848165b5755"&gt;by clicking here&lt;/a&gt;. It is unknown how this affects children who use Discord to this day. Discord recommends parents be aware of their child's use of the internet in order to keep them safe online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="4-advertisement-data-collection"&gt;4. Advertisement Data Collection&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Users are entitled to stop having data collected from Discord's advertisements on other services. Updates to the &lt;a href="https://discordapp.com/privacy?next"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; now entitle users to exercise opt-out programs administered by third-parties. Such parties include the &lt;a href="http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/"&gt;Network Advertising Initiative&lt;/a&gt; (NAI), and the more common &lt;a href="http://optout.aboutads.info/#/"&gt;Digital Advertising Alliance&lt;/a&gt; (DAA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new Privacy Policy is scheduled to be enacted on May 1st, 2017. Users must read and accept it in order to use their services, as well as the Terms Of Service. The Privacy Policy can be found &lt;a href="https://discordapp.com/privacy?next"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The Terms Of Service can be found &lt;a href="https://discordapp.com/terms?next"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The Support portal can be reached by clicking &lt;a href="https://support.discordapp.com/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="5-new-community-guidelines"&gt;5. New Community Guidelines&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Discord now has a Community Guidelines page, just like YouTube does. The guidelines can be found &lt;a href="https://discordapp.com/guidelines"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. These guidelines talk about the rules of Discord. They explain the consequences for violating such rules, which can include suspension of the service for a certain amount of time, and/or account deletion. They make it clear that misconduct is &lt;strong&gt;not tolerated&lt;/strong&gt;, and that they will incite consequences for those who disobey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="conclusion"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do you feel about these new policies? Perhaps the policies are too strict for you? Feel free to leave your thoughts down in the comments section below. If you would like to see more blog posts like this one, please subscribe so we can get the latest posts to you as soon as possible. Thank you for reading this article, and stay safe!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Aclevo Is Leaving YouTube, But Why? (OUTDATED)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Serious changes are going to be made in order to keep Aclevo alive. For one, our main source of revenue will be the blog instead of YouTube. I, Reasonably Selenium, the CEO of Aclevo, will be explaining why in a minute. We as a company will also be switching from&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/aclevo-is-leaving-youtube-but-why-outdated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a35871fa13f590f528517</guid><category>youtube</category><category>money</category><category>monetization</category><category>demonetization</category><category>income</category><category>dailymotion</category><category>hitbox</category><category>goals</category><category>annoucements</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1493852303730-955ff798ba12?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1493852303730-955ff798ba12?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" alt="Aclevo Is Leaving YouTube, But Why? (OUTDATED)"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Serious changes are going to be made in order to keep Aclevo alive. For one, our main source of revenue will be the blog instead of YouTube. I, Reasonably Selenium, the CEO of Aclevo, will be explaining why in a minute. We as a company will also be switching from YouTube to other services such as DailyMotion and HitBox. Before we begin, please understand that we have strong opinions about maintaining an effective budget in the surplus region. We really do not like losing one of our best sources of income that keeps us rolling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you all may know, YouTube has recently changed their policies regarding monetization. YouTube channels below 10k total views will no longer be able to receive revenue until they are able to get that amount of views. Unfortunately, getting popular does not happen overnight, and Aclevo heavily relied on this revenue in order to provide funding for the website and the domain. We may not be able to pay for the xyz domain due to the unforeseen circumstances, and may have to go back to using a free domain. We will keep you posted, and update you if and when "doomsday" comes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in all seriousness, we do have some solution to our revenue problems, which is our blog. We use the ads on our posts to pay for the website and domain. I am not qualified to share information about how much revenue we make. However, we as Aclevo hope to make enough revenue in order to pay for our necessities and keep the blog running. Our bloggers, including myself, work really hard in order to make sure content gets pushed out here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We as a company will no longer post our videos to YouTube. Instead, all videos will be uploaded and monetized on a video sharing service known as DailyMotion. Their company was founded in France in 2003, and has been growing as an alternative to YouTube ever since. Our Multi Channel Network, known as Freedom, currently support getting revenue on DailyMotion at the time of this post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also support HitBox, a video streaming service we may decide to use to stream Aclevo Live. One of our members showed interest in producing live shows in order to get more viewers. We thought it would be in our interest to start streaming in order to keep our fans happy. If you would like to see us live stream successfully for the first time, please let us know down in the comments below. We will be sure to produce quality content on the double.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for taking the time to read this post. If you would like to stay updated with us, please be sure to subscribe for more blog posts, and tell us in the comments what you think about the situation and what you think we should do next. Please be sure to check out our other posts to get more amazing content. Have a nice day, everyone!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>YouTube Monetization Threshold</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Not too long ago, Google posted on the YouTube Creators blog that they are adding a view threshold to serve ads on your videos, now they are saying in order to make any sort of revenue on your videos via ads you have to have at least 10,000 lifetime&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/youtube-monetization/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a2fd91fa13f590f528480</guid><category>youtube</category><category>monetization</category><category>threshold</category><category>demonetization</category><category>creators</category><category>money</category><category>revenue</category><category>content id</category><dc:creator>Nebula</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1521302200778-33500795e128?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1521302200778-33500795e128?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;q=80&amp;fm=jpg&amp;crop=entropy&amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;w=1080&amp;fit=max&amp;ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjExNzczfQ" alt="YouTube Monetization Threshold"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not too long ago, Google posted on the YouTube Creators blog that they are adding a view threshold to serve ads on your videos, now they are saying in order to make any sort of revenue on your videos via ads you have to have at least 10,000 lifetime video views on your channel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's quite a bummer for the average small YouTube Creator, as it usually takes at least over a year to rack up so many views on your channel. Though is that mostly a good thing or a bad thing, The good thing is that it gives YouTube enough information to determine if a channel is worthy of placing ads on their content. The bad thing is... you don't get ad revenue for quite some time, like that even matters how little you get during those early days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why did YouTube decide to do this you may ask, well, many large advertisers heard from a source called the Wall Street Journal that their ads were being shown on hate content such as ISIS videos and things of that nature, and they took action and decided to pull ads from YouTube all together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The culprit of these actions is Content ID, which is a flawed system. Said videos were being claimed via the Content ID system resulting in premium advertisements being shown on those videos, thus getting noticed by the Wall Street Journal, thus resulting in ads being pulled, thus the new view threshold being placed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I personally don't this this is a good solution to this problem as what I do believe is that Content ID should be fixed instead of adding a view threshold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will things be sorted out for the better soon? Who knows. &lt;br&gt;More updates on the situation will be posted as I find out about them.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Gentoo Linux Review</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As promised before, I've decided to go ahead and write about Gentoo. Like Arch, Gentoo is also one of the most customizable distributions of Linux, though it takes a bit more time to install than Arch due to having to compile literally everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gentoo has it's own build utility though,&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/gentoo-linux-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a307f1fa13f590f528493</guid><category>gentoo</category><category>linux</category><category>linux distrobution</category><category>GNU</category><category>arch linux</category><category>review</category><category>compiling</category><dc:creator>Nebula</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/gentoo-horizontal.png" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/gentoo-horizontal.png" alt="Gentoo Linux Review"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As promised before, I've decided to go ahead and write about Gentoo. Like Arch, Gentoo is also one of the most customizable distributions of Linux, though it takes a bit more time to install than Arch due to having to compile literally everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gentoo has it's own build utility though, that the name of slips my mind, it's easily accessed using the command emerge. Installing Gentoo is done completely through said command.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like Arch, It can be proven difficult for new users to install if they don't know how to partition the hard drive or how to use basic shell commands, it's best to read the installation guide if that's the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also like Arch, the most basic installation is a Kernel, Shell, and a copy of the GNU Compiler Collection. Installing other software is as simple as typing emerge then the name of the program unless the program is somehow not included in the source code repositories, using emerge automatically takes the system through the build steps to compile said program making the task much simpler.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My honest opinion on the score I shall give Gentoo, 7.9/10, due to the slow install process. I'd prefer Arch over Gentoo for that reason alone. Gentoo is mainly for people that like to have the binaries completely tailored to the hardware their PC has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How to be anonymous online (Using a VPN)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If I care about one thing about being online, then it must be privacy. A common mistake I always see is that people think if they are not doing anything wrong then they do not need to be safe. That's not a good mindset to use when browsing the web.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/how-to-be-anonymous-online-using-a-vpn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a2ec61fa13f590f528466</guid><category>vpn</category><category>anonymous</category><category>internet</category><category>intelligence</category><category>privacy</category><category>safety</category><category>policy</category><dc:creator>RXDesigns</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/anonvpn.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/02/anonvpn.jpg" alt="How to be anonymous online (Using a VPN)"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If I care about one thing about being online, then it must be privacy. A common mistake I always see is that people think if they are not doing anything wrong then they do not need to be safe. That's not a good mindset to use when browsing the web. A great solution for this is a VPN.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-s-a-vpn-and-why-should-i-care"&gt;What's a VPN and why should I care?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A VPN enables users to send and receive data across shared or public networks as if their computers were directly connected to the private network. Not only does this hide your IP-address, but also your location and websites you visit from your ISP. It's also useful for browsing websites that happen to be blocked by your ISP or website administrator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day you give access to your personal data to thousands of websites and services located all over the world. On the way to its final destination your data passes dozens of hops, routers and networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your data can be logged, monitored, analyzed and stored by your ISP, your network administrator, a site you visit, your network peers, or even worse, a hacker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, your network peers may be snooping and peeking on your private Internet activities, looking for a way to compromise you and damage your reputation. And a hacker who gave you a free access to his unsecured WiFi is waiting to take over your email account and gain access to your bank account.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="okay-this-sounds-scary-how-can-i-get-a-vpn"&gt;Okay, this sounds scary. How can I get a VPN?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of VPN providers out there, so I understand it's difficult to choose. (Trust me, I know. I had to do this myself.) Here are a few points that you need to consider when choosing a VPN:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logging of any kind (If your VPN provider keeps logs, it is a wise decision not to utilize their service.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Location of HQ (If your VPN provider is operating in a five, nine or fourteen-eyes country, you may want to reconsider. &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Five_Eyes"&gt;Read here why this matters.&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Their policies (Not everyone may want to do this, but for your privacy's sake I recommend you to check the VPN provider's ToS. Some of them may not care too much about your privacy or not at all, which is quite ironic.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Pom's Drop Party: A Minecrafter's Dream</title><description>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;iframe width="480" height="270" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BmC6qEDVXPU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;After finishing the Cool Roller Coaster Video which can be found in a previous post on this blog, Pom said he would be hosting another event. Enjoying my previous work featured on this blog, he offered me another chance to put my video editing skills to work. So I decided&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/poms-drop-party-a-minecrafters-dream/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c5a31db1fa13f590f5284b5</guid><category>minecraft</category><category>ThePom360</category><category>drop party</category><category>items</category><category>game</category><category>fun</category><dc:creator>Reasonably Selenium</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;iframe width="480" height="270" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BmC6qEDVXPU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;After finishing the Cool Roller Coaster Video which can be found in a previous post on this blog, Pom said he would be hosting another event. Enjoying my previous work featured on this blog, he offered me another chance to put my video editing skills to work. So I decided to get out my &lt;strong&gt;handy dandy&lt;/strong&gt; virtual camera, and started recording Pom's Drop Party. A drop party is a Minecraft minigame where players try to collect the most items, preferably valuable ones, and they get to keep all of them. Above is a video capturing the insane moments of this fantastic minigame.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>